<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
	<author>loki_79</author>
    <version>1.0.0.3</version>
	<title>
		<en>LumberJack</en>
		<de>Holzfäller</de>
		<fr>Bûcheron</fr>
	</title>

	<description>
<en><![CDATA[This mod adds some quality of life improvements to make felling trees with the chainsaw a little easier, but still retains enough realism to allow payment for selling the wood. The chainsaw can now shred tree stumps, and the “super strength” mode also offers the ability to completely remove trees.

Keyboard shortcuts:
- Hold ALT for temporary strength
- Double tap ALT to toggle super strength on/off

Features:
- Easily remove smaller pieces of wood, similar to removing thin branches
- Cutting speed and range of the chainsaw adjustable
- Adjustable object weight and shooting range (only when super power is active)
- Cutting trees anywhere on the map, even on areas that cannot be purchased (e.g. from the dealer)
- Display the weight of the viewed objects in the F1 menu
- Chainsaw can remove stumps (grind for 3 seconds) 

Changelog:
v1.0.0.2
- Added missing chainsaw cutting speed to the settings
v1.0.0.1
- Fixed an error that would prevent the mod starting on the Asian Map

Note:
- Super strength is currently disabled in multiplayer.
]]>
</en>
<de><![CDATA[Dieser Mod fügt einige Verbesserungen hinzu, welche das Fällen von Bäumen mit der Kettensäge erleichtern. Der Realismus bleibt weiterhin erhalten.  Die Kettensäge kann nun Baumstümpfe entfernen, und der "Superstärke"-Modus ermöglicht es zudem, Bäume vollständig zu entfernen.

Tastenkombinationen:
- ALT für temporäre Stärke gedrückt halten
- Tippe ALT doppelt zum Ein-/Ausschalten der Superstärke

Funktionen:
- Leichte Entfernung kleiner Holzstücke, ähnlich wie beim Entfernen von Ästen
- Einstellbare Geschwindigkeit und Reichweite der Kettensäge
- Einstellbares Baumstammgewicht und Aufnahmereichweite (nur bei aktiver Superstärke)
- Bäume können überall gefällt werden, auch auf ungekauften Flächen
- Anzeige des Gewichts, aufgehobener Gegenstände
- Kettensäge kann Stümpfe entfernen (3 Sekunden schneiden)

Changelog:
v1.0.0.2
- Fehlende Kettensägenschnittgeschwindigkeit zu den Einstellungen hinzugefügt
v1.0.0.1
- Fehler behoben, der das Starten des Mods auf der asiatischen Karte verhinderte

Anmerkung:
- Superstärke ist derzeit für den Mehrspielermodus deaktiviert
]]>
</de>
<fr><![CDATA[Ce mod ajoute des améliorations pour simplifier l'abattage des arbres avec une tronçonneuse tout en conservant suffisamment de réalisme pour que la vente du bois reste réaliste. La tronçonneuse peut désormais broyer les souches, et le mode "Super Force" permet aussi de supprimer complètement les arbres.

Raccourcis clavier :
- Maintenez ALT pour la force temporaire
- Appuyez deux fois sur ALT pour activer/désactiver la Super Force

Caractéristiques :
- Suppression facile des petites pièces de bois, similaire à l'élimination des branches fines
- Vitesse et portée de coupe de la tronçonneuse ajustables
- Masse des objets et portée de prise ajustables (uniquement lorsque la Super Force est activée)
- Coupez des arbres n'importe où sur la carte, même dans des zones non achetables (par exemple chez le concessionnaire)
- Affichage de la masse des objets consultés dans le menu F1
- La tronçonneuse peut supprimer les souches (broyage pendant 3 secondes)

Changelog :
v1.0.0.2
- Ajout de la vitesse de coupe manquante aux paramètres de la tronçonneuse
v1.0.0.1
- Correction d'une erreur empêchant le démarrage du mod sur la carte asiatique

Note :
- La Super Force est actuellement désactivée en mode multijoueur.
]]>
</fr>
	</description>

	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon_LumberJack.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="LumberJack.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>
	
	<actions>
		<action name="LUMBERJACK_STRENGTH" category="ONFOOT" axisType="HALF"/>
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="LUMBERJACK_STRENGTH" >
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>	
	<l10n filenamePrefix="language/l10n"/>
	
</modDesc>
