<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
	<author>loki_79</author>
    <version>1.0.0.3</version>
	<title>
		<en>LumberJack</en>
		<de>Holzfäller</de>
		<br>Lenhador</br>
	</title>

	<description>
<en><![CDATA[This mod adds some quality of life improvements to make felling trees with the chainsaw a little easier, but still retains enough realism to allow payment for selling the wood. The chainsaw can now shred tree stumps, and the “super strength” mode also offers the ability to completely remove trees.

Keyboard shortcuts:
- Hold ALT for temporary strength
- Double tap ALT to toggle super strength on/off

Features:
- Easily remove smaller pieces of wood, similar to removing thin branches
- Cutting speed and range of the chainsaw adjustable
- Adjustable object weight and shooting range (only when super power is active)
- Cutting trees anywhere on the map, even on areas that cannot be purchased (e.g. from the dealer)
- Display the weight of the viewed objects in the F1 menu
- Chainsaw can remove stumps (grind for 3 seconds) 

Changelog:
v1.0.0.2
- Added missing chainsaw cutting speed to the settings
v1.0.0.1
- Fixed an error that would prevent the mod starting on the Asian Map

Note:
- Super strength is currently disabled in multiplayer.
]]>
</en>
<de><![CDATA[Dieser Mod fügt einige Verbesserungen der Lebensqualität hinzu, um das Abholzen von Bäumen mit der Kettensäge etwas einfacher zu machen, behält aber immer noch genug Realismus, um die Bezahlung für den Verkauf des Holzes zu verdienen.  Die Kettensäge kann nun Baumstümpfe schleifen, und der 'Superstärke'-Modus bietet auch die Möglichkeit, Bäume vollständig zu löschen.

Tastenkombinationen:
- ALT für temporäre Stärke gedrückt halten
- Tippe ALT doppelt zum Ein-/Ausschalten der Superstärke

Merkmale:
- Leichte Zerstörung kleiner Holzstücke, ähnlich wie beim Entfernen von superfischen Ästen
- Einstellbare Geschwindigkeit und Reichweite der Kettensäge
- Einstellbare Objektmasse und Aufnahmereichweite (nur bei aktiver Superstärke)
- Bäume überall auf der Karte fällen, auch auf Land, das nicht gekauft werden kann (wie das Geschäft)
- Masse der angezeigten Objekte im F1-Menü anzeigen
- Kettensäge kann Stümpfe entfernen (3 Sekunden schleifen)

Changelog:
v1.0.0.2
- Fehlende Kettensägenschnittgeschwindigkeit zu den Einstellungen hinzugefügt
v1.0.0.1
- Fehler behoben, der den Start der Mod auf der asiatischen Karte verhinderte

Anmerkung:
- Superstärke ist derzeit im Mehrspielermodus deaktiviert.
]]>
</de>
<br><![CDATA[Este mod adiciona algumas melhorias na qualidade de vida para tornar o corte de árvores com a motosserra um pouco mais fácil, mas ainda mantém realismo suficiente para permitir o pagamento pela venda da madeira. A motosserra agora pode moer tocos de árvores, e o modo "super força" também oferece a capacidade de remover árvores completamente.

Atalhos de teclado:
- Segure ALT para força temporária
- Pressione ALT duas vezes para alternar a super força ligar/desligar

Recursos:
- Remova facilmente pedaços menores de madeira, semelhante à remoção de galhos finos
- Velocidade de corte e alcance da motosserra ajustáveis
- Peso dos objetos e alcance ajustáveis (somente com a super força ativada)
- Corte árvores em qualquer lugar do mapa, até mesmo em áreas que não podem ser compradas (ex.: na loja)
- Exibição do peso dos objetos visualizados no menu F1
- A motosserra pode remover tocos (moer por 3 segundos)

Alterações:
v1.0.0.2
- Adicionada a velocidade de corte da motosserra ausente às configurações
v1.0.0.1
- Corrigido um erro que impedia o mod de iniciar no mapa asiático

Nota:
- A superforça está atualmente desativada no modo multijogador.
]]>
</br>
		
	</description>

	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon_LumberJack.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="LumberJack.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>
	
	<actions>
		<action name="LUMBERJACK_STRENGTH" category="ONFOOT" axisType="HALF"/>
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="LUMBERJACK_STRENGTH" >
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>	
	<l10n filenamePrefix="language/l10n"/>
	
</modDesc>
